Guide to the Stanford University Poster Collection SC1030
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters
  - The Return of Sprocket Man. In 1975 he came to stop the mayhem. Now he's back...to finish the job. Think bicycle safety starting today! Parking and Transportation Office, 2002; 2003-014; 12.5 x 21 inches (Box B1)
    Sprocket Man created by Louis Hsu Saekow (class of '76).
  - The Rev. Hugh Black, D. D., Un-dated; 397; 10 x 13 inches (Box A2)
  - The Road to War. A fifty year commemortive exhibit on the beginning of World War II drawn from the collections of the Hoover Institution. September 1988--June 1989., 2003-037; 15 x 20 inches (Box B1)
  - "The Roar of the Grease-Paint- The Smell of the Crowd", 1968; 508-7; 11 x 17 inches (Box C6)
  - "The Romantic Young Lady", Undated; 504-7; 14 x 20 in (Box not specified)
  - The Roundtable at Stanford University. Anxious Times. Seeing Beyond a World of Perpetual Threats, 2006 Oct 24; 2009-018; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - The Roundtable at Stanford University. Courting Disaster. The Fight for Oil, Water and a Healthy Planet., 2007 Oct 13; 2009-019; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - "The Royal Family", Jan 30- Feb 1,1947; 511-6; 14 x 21 inches (Box C5)
  - "The School for Scandal", August 15 17, 1946; 511-5; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "The Sea Gull" by Checkov, 1945; 511-3; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - The Senior Class of Stanford '04: Patience, 1904; 513-75; 22.5 x 28.5 (Box D2)
  - the six millionth / libraries of stanford / Robert Creeley Archive October 1993 [poster celebrating acquisition of the six millionth "book" in the SU Libraries], 2008-005; 21.5 x 11.5 inches (Box C10)
  - The Spoken Word Collective, Stanford Concert Network and Women's Community Center present "Stacey-Ann Chin". Def-jam spoken word show., 39927; 2009-007; 12 x 18 inches (Box C6)
  - The Stanford Band "Stanford's Own" in Formal Concert, 1926 April 30; ARCH-2017-089 (Box TBD)
    Scope and Contents
    Band poster belonged to John Metts Willits.
  - The Stanford Center for Chicano Research presents the 7th Annual Ernesto Galarza Lecture. "Meztizaje: The Formation of The Chicanos" Julian Samora. Friday April 24, 1992, 2009-020; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
    Printed on 3 different paper stocks.
  - The Stanford Chamber Players, 1968; 202-31; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - The Stanford Committee on Black Performing Arts and the Kuumba Dance Ensemble present: Carnival '81. Thursday & Friday March 5 & 6, 1981; 2005-007; 8.5 x 14 inches (Box A3)
    From Kennell Jackson's papers; removed from frame
  - The Stanford Concert Band, 1965; 202-15; 11 x 16 inches (Box A1)
  - The Stanford Glee Club, 1937; 524-16; 13 x 19 in (Box not specified)
  - The Stanford Humanities Center Presents: the 1998 Marta Sutton Weeks Distinguished Visitor Neil Harris. Two talks: Envisioning Authority April 6, 1998; Building Ceremonies: Beginnings and Ends, April 8, 1998, 2171 (Box map case)
  - The Stanford Inn, Un-dated; 33; 22 x 14 inches (Box C1)
  - The Stanford Men's Glee Club Friday April 24 [1959] Dinkelspiel Auditorium, 524-21; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - The Stanford Presidential Symposium on Engineering and the Humanities: Special Effects. Feb. 11-12, [2000], 2003-032; 11.75 x 18.75 inches (Box B1)
  - The Stanford Quadrangles Design and Construction May 23--July 28, 1983. The Gallery Second Floor Cecil Green Library [exhibit poster], 2002-018; 14 x 18 inches (Box B1)
    2nd copy is mounted on board; came from ASUL collection
  - The Stanford Renaissance Band, 1969; 524-28; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - The Stanford Shakespeare Company presents: "The Two Gentlemen of Verona", Febuary 18-22, 2009; 2009-005; 11 x 17 inches (Box C6)
  - The Stanford Symphony, 1965; 202-9; 10 x 16 inches (Box A1)
  - "The Three Sisters", 1940; 513-22; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "The Time of Your Life", Un-dated; 511-53; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "The Torch Bearers", Un-dated; 513-36; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "The Trail", 1951; 511-26; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "The Trojan Women of Euripides", Un-dated; 5059; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - "The Two Gentlemen from Verona", 1906; 513-13; 16 x 14 inches (Box B3)
  - The Two Reservations: Western Thought, the Color Line, and the CRISIS OF THE NEGRO INTELLECTUAL, revisited. A symposium March 3-5, 1994, 2181; 17 x 22.5 inches (Box not specified)
    African and Afro-American Studies
  - The Two Reservations: Western Thought, the Color Line, and THE CRISIS OF THE NEGRO INTELLECTUAL, Revisited. A Symposium March 3-5, 1994., 21801; 17x22.5 inches (Box C1)
  - "The Uncalled for Feiffer Forum" and Forum Preview (Big Game Musical), 1968; 5102; 8 1/2 x 11 in (Box A3)
  - "The Vikings at Helgelend", Un-dated; 5057; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - The War- The Elections, 1968; 905-53; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - "The Well of Saints", 1959; 511-39; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "The Wild Duck", Un-dated; 513-33; 14 x 20 inches (Box C7)
  - The Works of William Morris, 1967; 2017; 17 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - The Workshop: a new journal of poetry, essays, prose, 1968; 514-12; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "The Yellow Jacket", Un-dated; 5076; 9 x 21 in (Box C6)
  - Theater at the Museum, 1967; 203-5; 12 x 19 inches (Box B1)
  - Theater of the Congressional Record, 1967; 5053; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Theater of the Congressional Record, 1968; 5054; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Theater of the Congressional Record, 1969; 5055; 8 1/2 x 11 in (Box not specified)
  - Theodore Morrison, 1966; 334; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - They Told Us Not to Sing. Arts of social change at Stanford. May 2000. ASSU Program board and others, 2003-022; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - thinkBIG; A conference on International Women's Health and Human Rights at Stanford Univeristy, February 1-3, 2008, 2008-007; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - #thisisartsintensive Photo Contest, 2013 Sep; 2015-012; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A6)
    Stanford University. Arts Intensive Program
  - #thisissophomorecollege Photo Contest, 2013 Sep; 2015-011; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A6)
    Stanford Sophomore College.
  - Thoughtful New Look: AMericans for Reappraisal of Far Eastern Policy, 1965; 113; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Three One-Act Plays, Un-dated; 502-4; 7 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Three Original One-Act Plays by Stanford Writers, 1948; 511-19; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "Thunder Rock", 1941; 513-23; 11 x 14 inches (Box A3)
  - TMU Cultural Arts Division Presents Criticsm and the Fine Arts. A Thursday Evening Series Oct. 17-Nov. 21 TMU Large Lounge [1968], 528-01; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - "To Have and To Lose" [also reads "Doctor Jordan will wear Bloomers in the Quad Tomorrow" by virtue of layout], Un-dated; 513-64; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
    copy 2 may be a reproduction
  - TO BEAT MAX: GET OUT THE VOTE! Cranston--Edwards tues. 3-4:40 ASSU Office [1968], 905-42; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
    Raffery was written in pencil after "MAX"
  - To Beat Max: Get Out the Vote., 1968; 905-42; 8 1/2 x 11 in (Box not specified)
  - To Promote Peace: Hoover Institution 75th Anniversary Exhibit, 19904; 215-1; 11 x 14 inches (Box not specified)
  - To Remote Peace: Hoover Institution 75 th Anniversary Exhibit, 1994; 215-01; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - To the Men of the University: Mr. John R. Mott, General Secretary, World's Student Christian Federation, 1901 Jan 11; 2015-027; 14.25 x 22.5 inches (Box C11)
  - Today Monday Monster Rally in honor of the passage of the amendment. Speeches by Dr. Jordan, Prof. Lewers, and Others. Biggest Barrel Fire Ever on the Campus. Meet at 7:30 pm for the Parade and "Whoop-'er-up" Rally., 1900; 526-01; 15 x 20.5 inches folded (Box C4)
  - Track and Field--All Southern California Track Team vs Varsity, 1906; 803-21; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Annual Handicap Field Day, Un-dated; 803-17; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Track and Field--California vs Stanford, Un-dated; 803-10; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--California vs Stanford, Un-dated; 803-12; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--California vs Stanford, Un-dated; 803-13; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--California vs Stanford, Un-dated; 803-26; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Freshmen Field Meet, 1905-; 803-1; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Freshmen vs Oakland High School, Un-dated; 803-20; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Freshmen vs Santa Rosa High School, Un-dated; 803-18; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Freshmen vs Santa Rosa High School, Un-dated; 803-23; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Interclass Track Meet, Un-dated; 803-9; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Intercollegiate Conference, 1910; 803-4; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Oakland Hich School vs stanford Freshmen, Un-dated; 803-33; 9 1/2 x 12 inches (Box map case)
  - Track and Field--Oakland vs Freshmen, Un-dated; 803-14; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Track and Field--Pomona college vs Varsity, Un-dated; 803-7; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Seniors and Juniors vs Sophomores and Freshmen, Un-dated; 803-24; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Six Mile Irish Marathon, 1910; 803-3; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Sixth Annual Interscholastic Meet, Un-dated; 803-19; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Stanford vs California, Un-dated; 803-16; 14x20 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Stanford vs California, 1905-; 803-2; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Stanford vs California, 1908; 803-15; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--Stanford vs California, 1910; 803-11; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--State Interscholastic Track Met, 1906; 803-8; 14x22 inches (Box map case)
  - Track and Field--U.S. Olympic Trials, 1960; 803-5; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Track and Field--University Handicap, 1906; 803-6; 9 1/2 x 12 inches (Box C8)
    One copy is 9 1/2 x 12 inches and the other is 14 x 22 inches Both are in C8
  - Track and Field Games- Oakland High School vs. Stanford Freshman, Un-dated; 803-22 (Box A4)
  - Training House Concert by the Varsity Mandolin and Glee Clubs, Ladies' Mandolin and Glee Clubs. Mr. Culver and Mr. Riley will do Specialties. Friday Evening Mar. 10 in Chapel [possibly 1899], 524-44; 14 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Travel Talk on California, 1900; 310; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - "Trelawney of the Wells", 1921; 5041; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Tresidder Gambling Night, Un-dated; 528-4; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Tresidder Gamblling Night, 8-12. Admission $.50. Poster by Sherri Smith., 1964 May 8-12; 528-04; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union--Community Meeting, 1969; 528-2; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union--Criticism and the Fine Arts, 1968; 528-1; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union--The Critic and Popular Entertainment, 1969; 528-3; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Tresidder Union's Twentieth Anniversary Winter Fete A Celebration of the Arts [calendar of events], 1982; 2006-056; 18 x 24 inches (Box C4)
    found in 4digit backlog
  - Tryouts for "Orphee" and "Purgatory", 1962; 513-31; 9 x 24 inches (Box C7)
  - Tryouts for "Orphee" and "Purgatory", 1962; 513-31; 9 x 24 inches (Box not specified)
  - Tuesday at Stanford, 1959; 323; 13x14 inches (Box map case)
  - Tuesday at Stanford, 1959; 322; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - Tuesday Evening Series, 1965; 327; 9 1/2x12 inches (Box A2)
  - Tuesday Evening Series, 1968; 341; 9x14 inches (Box A2)
  - Tuesday Noon Recital, 1959; 202-1; 11 x 14 inches (Box A1)
  - "Twelfth Night", Un-dated; 513-53; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "Twelfth Night", Un-dated; 513-54; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Twentieth Annual Carnot Debate, 1913; 521-2; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - U.S. Policy and the Middle East Crisis, 1968; 337; 14x22 inches (Box C1)
  - "Under Milk Wood", Un-dated; 511-56; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "Under the Gaslight", Un-dated; 5034; 22 x 28 inches (Box D2)
  - "Under the Gaslight", 1960; 5083; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Undergraduate Education, 1969; 22; 22 x 14 inches (Box C1)
  - University Chapel, Un-dated; 388; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - University Film Series, 1967; 16; 11 x 13 inches (Box A6)
  - University Orchestra Concert, 1902-; 524-11; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - University Orchestra Concert Thursday, May 9th in the Chapel. Mrs. E. W. Schneider, soloist, 1910 May 9; 524-48; 22 x 14 inches (Box C5)
  - Up Against the Screen. The Battle of Algiers. Perhaps the most important political film of the decade. Tuesday April 8 [1969] Mem Aud. Sponsored by SDS and the Resistance., 525-03; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - "Up, Up, and Away", 1969; 524-29; 5 1/2 x 8 1/2 inches (Box not specified)
  - URGENT ALL-CAMPUS FRIDAY NOON MEETING TO DISCUSS TRUSTEES' COURT INJUNCTION AGAINST APRIL 3 MOVEMENT. [1969], 527-07; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - "Vaudeville", Un-dated; 513-65; 28 x 20 inches (Box C7)
  - Visual Arts Services calendar [version not used but provided to U. Archives] 2004, featuring image of cactus garden, 2006-001; 11x17 inches (Box B2)
  - Visual Arts Services calendar, featuring image of horse (Baja) at the Red Barn, 2005; 2006-002; 12x19 inches (Box C4)
  - Visual Arts Services calendar, featuring drawing of Memorial Church facade and adjacent arcades and border of sandstone blocks, 2006-; 2006-003; 13x20 inches (Box B2)
  - Viva El Cinco de Mayo! E Stanford, 1989; 532-06; 11x17 inches (Box A2)
  - Volleyball (Men's)--2011 Season, 2011-007; 14x22 inches (Box B2)
    Athletics -- volleyball
  - Volleyball (Women's)/Soccer (Women's), 2011 Sep 9; 2011-007; 14x22 inches (Box B2)
  - Volleyball (Women's), signed, 1997; Accession ARCH-2016-133.05 (Box D2)
  - Volleyball (Women's), signed, 2004; Accession ARCH-2016-133.04 (Box A4)
  - "Volpone", Un-dated; 511-55; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Volunteers in Asia, 1968; 530-21; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - Vote, 1969; 905-67; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Vote Coach Montgomery. Mayor of Bracketville. www.nike.com/bracketville, 2001 or 2002; 2003-024; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Votes for Women, Un-dated; 9505-15; 18 x 26 inches (Box C11)
  - Want to know... info fair Stanford University Llibraries, 1994; 2002-006; 11 x 17 inches (Box B1)
  - We're Going to Oregon, 1968; 905-56; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - Weapons Crisis Week presented by the Stanford Arms Control and Disarmament Forum, 1982 Apr; 2006-054; 12.25 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - Weapons Crisis Week May presented by the Stanford Arms Control and Disarmament Forum, 1981 May; 2006-055; 17.25 x 22.5 inches (Box C4)
  - Wedgewood Porcelain, Un-dated; 35; 9x12 inches (Box A6)
  - Wednesday lectures in art, 1968; 203-9; 18 x 24 inches (Box C1)
  - Wednesday lectures in art, 1967 Autumn; 203-6; 18 x 24 inches (Box C1)
  - Wednesday lectures in art, 1966 Spring; 203-2; 16 x 24 inches (Box C11)
  - Wednesday lectures in art, 1966 Winter; 203-1; 16 x 24 inches (Box C1)
  - Wednesday lectures in art, 1967 Winter; 203-3; 18 x 23 inches (Box C11)
  - Weisburg. Sullivan. Kelman. Karlan. A Gilbert's and Sullivan Production, Slacking Student Hidden Dean. Saturday April 28 [2001], 2003-030; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - What Choice Do You Have, 1969; 373; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - "What Every Woman Knows", Un-dated; 513-38; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - What Is God Like?, Un-dated; 410; 9x12 inches (Box A2)
  - What Should Be Done Now?, 1968; 355; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Where are the radicals at? What are they up to? Come help us decide. SDS meeting Mondays 7:30 Branner Dining Room, 1968; 525-02; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - Why do you want to join Raagapella? A. Fame B. Fun C. Fortune D. Destiny / Stanford Raagapella presents slumraag millionaire / Auditions: Sept. 23 and 24 [2009], 2009-021; 11 x 15.5 inches (Box A5)
  - Why Should I Care About Syria?, 2013 Apr; 2015-010; 5.5 x 8.5 inches (Box A6)
    Stanford Stand
  - "Will Shakespeare", Un-dated; 5075; 11 x 14 inches (Box A3)
  - William Stafford Reading His Own Poetry, 1969; 377; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - "Winterset", 1948; 513-29; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Wither the Novel?, 1965; 329; 9 x 12 inches (Box A2)
  - Woman's Edition The Daily Palo Alto Stanford University April 22, 1903-, 514-4; 11 x 16 inches (Box B1)
    Includes drawing of a woman in cap and gown with inner quad behind her
  - Women of Color at the Center; the Third Natonal Conference on Women of Color and the Law. October 1990, 415; 18 x 18 inches (Box D2)
  - Women's Book and Art Fair. Sale and auction of books by and about women and works of art created by women. May 10 [no year]. To benefit the Stanford Center for Research on Women Library and Publication Fund., 2006-042; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Women's League Dues Payable Here, Un-dated; 26; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Working Against Rape: Current Research and Strategies for Change. Stanford University, Oct. 5-10, 1981, 2006-045; 11 x 17.5 inches (Box B2)
  - Workshop: the literary magazine, 1968; 514-13; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Woyzeck in German, 1968; 339; 11x17 inches (Box A2)
  - Ye Chester Miracle Plays, 1911; 513-16; 15 x 26 inches (Box D2)
  - "Yeats Festival- Four Plays of the Cuchulain Cycle", 1969; 513-32; 11 x 17 inches (Box A4)
  - Yiddish Poetry in English Translation, Un-dated; 412; 14x22 (Box C2)
  - "You and I", Un-dated; 513-60; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - You Can Do Something- Give Blood, Un-dated; 905-14; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - You Don't Look Mexican: A Play by Julie Padilla, 1998; 532-01; 11x17 inches (Box A2)
  - You Never Can Tell, 1907; 905-2; 9 x 10 inches (Box A4)
  - "You Touched Me!", Un-dated; 513-45; 13 x 20 inches (Box C7)
  - You've always been on the leading edge. So you'll definitely want to knonw what's new at the Stanford Libraries for 1997/98., 2002-010; 12 x 18 inches (Box B1)
  - YR's Present George Christopher, Un-dated; 530-27; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - Yvor winters Centenary. Stanford Humanities Center, 2000 Nov 16-18; 2003-020; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - YWCA Christmas Fair, Un-dated; 530-19; 19 x 24 inches (Box C8)
  - Stanford Calendar, 2013-2014; Accessin ARCH-2017-029 (Box Tube 1)
  - 30th Annual Johnson Symposium, 2015 Oct 9; Accession ARCH-2016-142; 2 poster(s) (Box A5)
  - Stanford Band "Stanford's Own" in Formal Concert, 1926 Apr 30; Accession ARCH-2018-089; 1 poster(s) (Box A5)